(Howard:)...went into my first anaphylactic shock,
had to be rushed to the hospital...
(Howard:)...came home, celebrated with a Snickers,
went into my second anaphylactic shock.
(Raj:)When did you figure out
you're allergic to nuts?
(Howard:)Sometime around the third Almond Joy.
Okay, wanna start loading this stuff
into the truck?
(Howard:)Yeah, I guess.
Hey, would you do me a favor?
Go on ahead.
(Howard:)I just want one last moment alone
in my old room.
(Leonard:)We're not standing outside by the U-Haul
while you fondle yourself.
(Howard:)Fine, let's go.
(Penny:)Hey, what brings you in?
(Sheldon:)Penny, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to have a conversation about girls.
(Penny:)Had a feeling we'd have a talk like this
sooner or later.
(Penny:)Are you finally getting fuzz in weird places?